

YEISON ARANGO ZAPATA

• DETAILS •

CRA 77 # 60 - 45 Medellin, 32746 Colombia 3197538538

jasonarangozapata@gmail.com

• LINKS •

<u>LinkedIn</u>

o SKILLS o

JavaScript

HTML5

CSS3

React

Redux

Git

LANGUAGES

Spanish

English

HOBBIES

Video Games

Series

Books

Music

PROFILE

I'm a Front-end developer with 9+ years of experience. I'm passionate, creative, disciplined, and in constant pursuit of self-development, willing to learn new concepts and techniques to develop functional and effective solutions.

I have a wide range of Knowledge in HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, JQuery, ReactJS, Redux, GIT, among others. I'm always looking for knowledge regarding new technologies especially to grow professionally. I'm good at working in a team, I'm a very helpful and fast learner, always trying to improve teamwork. All the time I'm in the search of the best solutions, looking for excellence and high quality.

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Sr. Front-End Developer at Team International, Medellin

July 2018 — Present

Front-end Developer, working on different modules to manage the supply chain services offered by the client developing a lot of new features, and supporting the different modules.

Tech stack: JavaScript, ReactJS, GraphQL, React-Apollo, Redux, ImmutableJS, Webpack, HTML5, SASS, Git, Jest.

SSR. Web UI Developer at Globant, Medellin

February 2017 — July 2018

I performed as WebUI Developer working on a virtual bank application. I was working on Mortgages and Insurances modules delivered all the customer requests assigned to me.

Tech Stack: React, Redux, Immutable, Webpack, Jest, Git, HTML5.

Front-End Developer at Integro, Medellin

May 2015 — February 2017

Role Description: I performed as a Front-End Developer and Team Leader in charge to redesign a medical application used to help a lot of patients improve their heart health according to their physical and emotional health state. Manage the team and the tasks to deliver properly all the customer requirements.

Tech Stack: ReactJS, Webpack, HTML5, CSS3, ChartsJS, NodeJS, Git, GitHub, MongoDB

FullStack Developer at Yuxi Global, Medellin

February 2013 — April 2015

I worked as a Full-stack developer on a Project for an e-Learning Company to manage all the e-Books and process the information for each e-Book. I supported python services to process image rendering, image sizes, and compress files to package all e-Books' information.

Tech Stack: Xquery, JavaScript, JQuery, MarkLogic, Git, Unfuddle, CSS3, HTML5, Bootstrap.

EDUCATION

Software Engineer, Tecnológico de Antioquia, Medellin

June 2018 — Present

Analysis and Software Development Technology, SENA, Medellin

January 2010 — June 2012

★ VOLUNTEER EXPERIENCE

Spearker: React Week, Medellin

March 2018 — March 2018

I have performed as Speaker in the React Week event, talking about React, Redux, and ImmutableJS basics. Showing how to integrate all of these in a simple ToDo list application and talking about all the features of these technologies.

InspiraMed, Medellin

March 2020 — June 2020

I had the opportunity to work on the mechanical fans team, writing the ReactJS application with an excellent development team. This React application has the goal to show different charts related to the oxygen volume, heart health, and another chart to support the COVID-19 disease attendance in the hospitals.

¶ REFERENCES

Andres Ochoa from Globant

+57 3007867609

Andres Felipe Betancur from TEAM International

+57 3013614265